<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://aask.ltd/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:29:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aask.ltd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON_Coin_Challenge</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/defcon_coin_challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:29:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/defcon_coin_challenge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the DEF CON Maker&amp;rsquo;s Community DEF CON Coin Challenge, where the programs are made up, and the filament doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. I&amp;rsquo;m your host BadAask Questions and I&amp;rsquo;m here to teach you about what adventure awaits inside the walls of this twice-only experience in 2024 at DEF CON 32 in the LVCC. In this workshop we will be exploring using CODE to write, yes you read that right, WRITE, your 3d models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hell0_world</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/hell0_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:39:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/hell0_world/</guid>
      <description>COMING SOON&#xA;AN ADVENTURE BETWEEN TWO MIDWEST SECDSM MEMBERS AS THEY DISSECT A TUYA WEATHER STATION.&#xA;THIS IS A PLACEHOLDER PAGE FOR OUR BSIDES/DEFCON WRITEUP AND WILL BE FILLED OUT IN THE COMING WEEKS.&#xA;COMING SOON</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ftc_fancy_lights</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/ftc_fancy_lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:49:17 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/ftc_fancy_lights/</guid>
      <description>Illuminating Productivity: My Journey with FTC Fancy Lights Hey there First Tech Challenge enthusiasts! For the past month I&amp;rsquo;ve been hyperfocusing on building this special project for FTC Iowa/Nebraska&amp;rsquo;s Championship at the XTreme Arena in Coralville Iowa. Presenting: The &amp;ldquo;FTC Fancy Lights&amp;rdquo;! These aren&amp;rsquo;t just any ordinary lights; they&amp;rsquo;re a blend of art, technology, and a bit of magic. Let me take you through the captivating world of my 8-sided infinity mirror creation, where every reflection tells a story of innovation and creativity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbot0_code</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 10:09:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_code/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s a bar robot without code? In this writeup we will be exploring the world of how we coded Señor Drinknstein using a Raspberry Pi Pico, and some mosfets! We will discuss why we chose the bill of materials we did, and some of the challenges we faced with said BOM. If you see any code in here that you would like to use for yourself feel free to take advantage of the free code!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbot1_part_0 Writeup for Supercon 2023</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot1_part_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 10:03:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot1_part_0/</guid>
      <description>Meet Señor Drinknstein Jr. (Junior) Placeholder for writeup of the second iteration of our barbot for the DC Shenanigans RentAnAssassin party in the Rain-man suite at Caesar&amp;rsquo;s Palace before DEF CON 31.&#xA;Outline Hardware upgrades Now with 100% more MOSFETS Now with 100% more PWM controller Code updates from last year MAJOR Ux upgrades Pulled back on Minimum Viable Product Photo Walkthru Let&amp;rsquo;s walk through some photos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 09:07:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/about/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. whoami? I&amp;rsquo;m Aask! Up to all the things that are fun and interesting. I created this website out of frustration of hackaday.io not being flexible enough. So I thought, instead of figuring out how to better use their services, why not learn an entire new technology stack called Hugo!&#xA;Now I&amp;rsquo;m here, updating this about me page, and have everything hooked up through gitpages.&#xA;NOTE: THIS IS NOT MY RESUME.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical_adapter</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/medical_adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:59:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/medical_adapter/</guid>
      <description>Union Medico Autoinjector Adapter One of the things I have to do regularly to maintain my health is take an injeciton intramuscularly once a week. While many are okay just doing this free hand, and others go in to their doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices to get it done, I picked up a Union Medico autoinjector. It&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty cool, it holds a standard syringe and drops it in to the muscle at the same pressure every time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Señor Plantnstein Lives!</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:51:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_part3/</guid>
      <description>Placeholder to talk about code changes made and upgrades made to the codebase for improvement of functionality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinkbot_part2</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 22:02:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0_part2/</guid>
      <description>Part 2 - Señor Drinknstein In part two we finish the build and set off for DEF CON!&#xA;Talk about the issues with the log file&#xA;What better way to open the second post with some red white and blue eh? Had to put together a batch of pis with headers and got this glamor shot. CONTINUED HERE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinkbot</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 18:41:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/barbot0/</guid>
      <description>Señor Drinknstein Comes to LIFE Señor Drinknstein started with an idea to use peristaltic pumps to serve various beverages, and has become so much more. For DEF CON 30 we worked to create a system of hardware and firmware that would give the end user a memorable experience while serving them a unique drink in a unique way at a unique event around unique people.&#xA;Because this is a finished project and I am ~lazy~ efficient, I&amp;rsquo;m going to type everything up here in most likely one go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First!</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 21:36:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>First post This is my first post to this website woohoo! I know how to do things. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://aask.ltd/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aask.ltd/contact/</guid>
      <description> First Name Last Name Email Powered by fabform.io&#xA;Notify Aask! </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
